exeideas.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - EXEIdeas – Let's Your Mind Rock

The privacy of my visitors to [www.exeideas.com](http://www.exeideas.com/ "EXEIdeas - Let's Your Mind Rock") is important to me. At [www.exeideas.com](http://www.exeideas.com/ "EXEIdeas - Let's Your Mind Rock"), I recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information I receive and collect when you use visit [www.exeideas.com](http://www.exeideas.com/ "EXEIdeas - Let's Your Mind Rock"), and how I safeguard your information.I never sell any kind of personal information to third parties or use this data for any illegal activities.

## Log Files:

As with most other websites, I collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Time Warner), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited my site and which pages you visit.

## Cookies and Web Beacons:

I do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit this site.

I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Los Angeles restaurants to Los Angeles residents, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing web development ads to someone who frequents web design sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.

However, this can affect how you are able to interact with my site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

## Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## Google AdSense:

The Google’s AdSense program uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables this site to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Email Addresses:

Should you [Contact Us](http://www.exeideas.com/p/contact-us.html "Contact EXEIdeas Support") me or subscribe to any of my information services via email, I will never sell or give away your email address.
